

# **PROFILE**

Skilled full stack developer with 5+ years of experience, and 2+ years of experience with data analysis and artificial intelligence. Recognized for hard working behaviors and love to learn and adapt. Also proven on multiple occasions to raise money for events and help gather sponsorships.

#### **CONTACT**

PHONE:

1(925)-448-5457

WEBSITE:

https://neelr.dev

GITHUB:

https://github.com/neelr

EMAIL:

neel.redkar@outlook.com

#### **HOBBIES**

Learning new skills and technologies Organizing Hackathons Origami Listening to Music Boy Scouts Debate

## **LANGUAGES**

Python: Keras, TensorFlow, Flask Node.js: React/React Native, Next.js, MongoDB, Express, Electron Bash, Vim, C, C++, Java, SQL, HTML/CSS

# NEEL REDKAR

Full Stack Developer and Data Scientist

# **EDUCATION**

Diablo Vista College

2018 - Current

4.0 GPA Taken Intro to Computer Science and Programming with Java (Equivalent of AP COMPSCI)

Dougherty Valley High School 2019 – 2023

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

AngelHacks Organizer Director Of Tech 2019–2019

2019–2019
Successfully organized a hackathon in Los Angeles to help computer science

education, raising over \$15,000 total with 130+ participants.

Hack The Fog Tech Team

2019-2020

The first high school hackathon to ever happen in San Francisco with 70+ attendees helping increase the amount of tech education inside of San Fransisco.

## **PROJECTS**

# Smart Recycle

This is an app that uses machine learning and image recognition to help people sort their recycling between trash, recycling, and compost. This project is on the App Store and won 2nd place in the statewide Science Fair.

#### Markei

This is an easy way for people to shorten URL's or even just make a fast website. This stores the link and a password, so you can edit it, and either redirects you to a link, or shows a markdown document.

#### RegHack

A self-hosted website that people can use to keep track of their hackathon attendees, allowing for simple QR code check-in, using MongoDB and allows for mass mailing.